

Lucas Gabriel Tamburlini

Concepción del Uruguay - Entre Ríos - Argentina

Email - lucastamburlini@gmail.com

Phone - +54 9 3442 644674

GitHub - github.com/lucastamburlini

LinkedIn - www.linkedin.com/in/lucasgabrieltamburlini

Portfolio - lucastamburlini.vercel.app

Professional Summary

Full Stack Junior Developer and QA Tester with experience in Web Development projects and previous experience in Human Resources. I have teamwork skills, data analysis and agile methodologies such as Scrum. Knowledge in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Sass, Bootstrap, Redux, Next.js, Tailwind CSS, TypeScript, Node.js, Express, Sequelize, MongoDB and PostgreSQL technologies. Also, experience in design tools such as Adobe Photoshop, Canva, CorelDRAW and Figma. As a QA Tester, I have experience in Exploratory and Conventional Testing methodologies, as well as in the use of tools such as Mocha, Jest, Playwright and Gherkin for automated testing.

Featured projects

♣ Flexwork LATAM (ene. 2024 - feb. 2024)

I led the development of a web platform that connects projects, professionals and companies. We used React and Tailwind CSS for the design, and implemented authentication and file management functions with Firebase. In addition, we created the backend with Node.js, Express and Sequelize to manage the application logic, and PostgreSQL for the database.

Access link - https://www.flexworklatam.com/

EducaStream (oct. 2023 - nov. 2023)

Together with three colleagues we created a microlearning education website with React. We used CSS Module for the design. We implemented a payment gateway with Stripe. We used Firebase for data storage and authentication and login management in the project. In addition, we used a PostgreSQL database for the project.

Access link - https://educastream.vercel.app/

Visit lucastamburlini.vercel.app to learn more about my projects.

Experience

Lemiro Pablo Pietroboni S.A. - Human Resources Soft Analyst (may 2022 – may 2023)

- ✓ I managed the human capital of the poultry processing plant with 300 employees, implementing search and selection strategies, education and training, and improving communication between departments with project management tools such as Trello and Management Committees.
- ✓ I contributed directly to improve the organizational climate and designed training and development plans, using human resources management software such as PDA Assessment.

♣ Fadel S.A. - Human Resources Generalist Analyst (may 2021 – may 2022)

✓ I managed the human capital of the poultry processing plant with 300 employees, implementing search and selection strategies, education and training, and improving communication between departments with project management tools such as Trello and Management Committees.

- ✓ I supervised the daily attendance control and managed the follow-up of absenteeism, illnesses and ART complaints, working in collaboration with health professionals. I used attendance tracking tools such as Microsoft Excel to ensure accurate and timely recording of data.
- ✓ I established an orderly work environment and drafted disciplinary sanctions in coordination with the company's legal team, using Microsoft Office tools to ensure disciplinary processes were carried out efficiently and following established legal guidelines.

Call Center Derudder Hnos. SRL - Technical Assistant (nov 2015 - may 2021)

✓ I led a call center team, supervised indicators and strategies to improve performance. I generated reports and provided support in sales and customer service at national and international level in the transportation sector, using internal and Google tools.

Education

Henry

✓ Full Stack Developer (Completed)

Universidad de Belgrano

✓ University Analyst in Human Capital Management (Completed)

Language

Spanish · Native
English B1 · Intermediate

Skills

Front-End: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Sass, Bootstrap, Redux, Next.js, Tailwind CSS, TypeScript.

Back-End: Node.js, Express, Sequelize, Java.

Database: MongoDB, PostgreSQL.

Design: Adobe Photoshop, Canva, CorelDRAW, Figma.

Agile Methodologies: Scrum.

Testing: Postman, Mocha, Jest, Playwright, Gherkin, Exploratory Testing, Conventional Testing

Methodologies.

Additional Tools: Trello, Jira.